{"subjectID":1,"researchID":"SonificationResearch","dateTime":"2020-12-23T10:12:46.1799676+01:00","answers":[{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 1 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":33.7500038,"questionAnswerTime":33.75},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 2 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":40.09914,"questionAnswerTime":40.09914},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 3 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":46.6913528,"questionAnswerTime":46.6913528},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 4 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":53.805233,"questionAnswerTime":53.805233},{"question":"Can the participant solve sequence 5 correctly?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":60.271862,"questionAnswerTime":60.271862},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":90.2046661,"questionAnswerTime":94.43384},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":90.2046661,"questionAnswerTime":94.43384},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.45212,"questionAnswerTime":98.92682},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":90.2046661,"questionAnswerTime":94.43384},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.45212,"questionAnswerTime":98.92682},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":100.945259,"questionAnswerTime":105.074333},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":90.2046661,"questionAnswerTime":94.43384},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.45212,"questionAnswerTime":98.92682},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":100.945259,"questionAnswerTime":105.074333},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":107.092636,"questionAnswerTime":109.975807},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":90.2046661,"questionAnswerTime":94.43384},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.45212,"questionAnswerTime":98.92682},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":100.945259,"questionAnswerTime":105.074333},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":107.092636,"questionAnswerTime":109.975807},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":111.993904,"questionAnswerTime":114.744331},{"question":"What is the mimimal noticable diffrence for this participant?","answer":"9.895554","questionAskTime":114.756744,"questionAnswerTime":114.756744},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":90.2046661,"questionAnswerTime":94.43384},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.45212,"questionAnswerTime":98.92682},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":100.945259,"questionAnswerTime":105.074333},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":107.092636,"questionAnswerTime":109.975807},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":111.993904,"questionAnswerTime":114.744331},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":114.765457,"questionAnswerTime":117.349525},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"11.32312","questionAskTime":117.358177,"questionAnswerTime":120.583496},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"2.932378","questionAskTime":120.585243,"questionAnswerTime":121.77652},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"8.78526","questionAskTime":121.778336,"questionAnswerTime":122.823166},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"11.06929","questionAskTime":122.824875,"questionAnswerTime":124.537224},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"3.773999","questionAskTime":124.539093,"questionAnswerTime":125.739647},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"5.582195","questionAskTime":125.741364,"questionAnswerTime":126.834045},{"question":"What is the error in condition 1?","answer":"11.80452","questionAskTime":126.835777,"questionAnswerTime":127.840363},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":90.2046661,"questionAnswerTime":94.43384},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.45212,"questionAnswerTime":98.92682},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":100.945259,"questionAnswerTime":105.074333},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":107.092636,"questionAnswerTime":109.975807},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":111.993904,"questionAnswerTime":114.744331},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":114.765457,"questionAnswerTime":117.349525},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":127.84063,"questionAnswerTime":131.205353},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":90.2046661,"questionAnswerTime":94.43384},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.45212,"questionAnswerTime":98.92682},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":100.945259,"questionAnswerTime":105.074333},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":107.092636,"questionAnswerTime":109.975807},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":111.993904,"questionAnswerTime":114.744331},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":114.765457,"questionAnswerTime":117.349525},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":127.84063,"questionAnswerTime":131.205353},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 2 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":131.221222,"questionAnswerTime":134.253433},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"8.602325","questionAskTime":134.261719,"questionAnswerTime":138.367081},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"8.740013","questionAskTime":138.369186,"questionAnswerTime":140.87439},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"1.838646","questionAskTime":140.876389,"questionAnswerTime":142.454712},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"11.07294","questionAskTime":142.4567,"questionAnswerTime":143.662155},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"5.072495","questionAskTime":143.664078,"questionAnswerTime":144.88678},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"8.924593","questionAskTime":144.888809,"questionAnswerTime":145.7282},{"question":"What is the error in condition 2?","answer":"11.71438","questionAskTime":145.730179,"questionAnswerTime":146.759842},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":90.2046661,"questionAnswerTime":94.43384},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.45212,"questionAnswerTime":98.92682},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":100.945259,"questionAnswerTime":105.074333},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":107.092636,"questionAnswerTime":109.975807},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":111.993904,"questionAnswerTime":114.744331},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":114.765457,"questionAnswerTime":117.349525},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":127.84063,"questionAnswerTime":131.205353},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 2 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":131.221222,"questionAnswerTime":134.253433},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 2?","answer":"5","questionAskTime":146.760086,"questionAnswerTime":149.328552},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":90.2046661,"questionAnswerTime":94.43384},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.45212,"questionAnswerTime":98.92682},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":100.945259,"questionAnswerTime":105.074333},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":107.092636,"questionAnswerTime":109.975807},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":111.993904,"questionAnswerTime":114.744331},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":114.765457,"questionAnswerTime":117.349525},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":127.84063,"questionAnswerTime":131.205353},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 2 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":131.221222,"questionAnswerTime":134.253433},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 2?","answer":"5","questionAskTime":146.760086,"questionAnswerTime":149.328552},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 3 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":149.34584,"questionAnswerTime":152.3376},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"8.544638","questionAskTime":152.346558,"questionAnswerTime":160.5106},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"9.811221","questionAskTime":160.512573,"questionAnswerTime":163.012482},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"11.7271","questionAskTime":163.014526,"questionAnswerTime":165.079468},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"4.579751","questionAskTime":165.081451,"questionAnswerTime":166.80954},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"9.4603","questionAskTime":166.811554,"questionAnswerTime":168.2146},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"11.24958","questionAskTime":168.216644,"questionAnswerTime":169.259933},{"question":"What is the error in condition 3?","answer":"9.776218","questionAskTime":169.2619,"questionAnswerTime":170.248474},{"question":"Do you have any visual impairment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":1.92174375,"questionAnswerTime":25.0594482},{"question":"Do you have any auditory impairtment?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":25.0837822,"questionAnswerTime":26.76586},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":62.27431,"questionAnswerTime":65.97873},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":67.99686,"questionAnswerTime":72.78796},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":74.80457,"questionAnswerTime":77.02918},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":79.04733,"questionAnswerTime":84.22838},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":86.24643,"questionAnswerTime":88.18618},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":90.2046661,"questionAnswerTime":94.43384},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":96.45212,"questionAnswerTime":98.92682},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":100.945259,"questionAnswerTime":105.074333},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":107.092636,"questionAnswerTime":109.975807},{"question":"Are you able to distinguish the sound origin?","answer":"No","questionAskTime":111.993904,"questionAnswerTime":114.744331},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 1 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":114.765457,"questionAnswerTime":117.349525},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 1?","answer":"4","questionAskTime":127.84063,"questionAnswerTime":131.205353},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 2 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":131.221222,"questionAnswerTime":134.253433},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 2?","answer":"5","questionAskTime":146.760086,"questionAnswerTime":149.328552},{"question":"Do you understand the condition 3 instruction?","answer":"Yes","questionAskTime":149.34584,"questionAnswerTime":152.3376},{"question":"How confident did you feel in your ability to estimate the sound origin in condition 3?","answer":"2","questionAskTime":170.2488,"questionAnswerTime":172.777832}]}